jhal hai
ki lecture diya welcome you to 8th
world war isse related question of the
answer is question on my screen key
me kuch such team series on screen
questions wb etc approaching nehru
bridge mist akhilesh about to enter the
grains from the opposite side you should
increase pen drive from the bridge as fast as
possible with children every girl
crosshair as the bridge and day famous foot
on the head light and pass then reached home
continues to indicate young man coming please
answer this question on screen is the third
question of the day in this meaning in the day
you can be a part of this free mode tours
the last date of the question is under
participate in this exciting prizes
and I request you to join with your
family and friends very important to
make your loved ones the road is well to
switch of unity to make lord dynasty we
request you to kindly join this  Campaign
with your family and friends and make them
and make roads by contributing in
like subscribe related to daily routine
questions related to be a part of this
and knowledge questions will be interpreted
from the opposite side on one subscribe
and you saw that enter and you
saw that the other one from the other side
that he is also going to enter in this dress now
this one from the side so what will you do at that
time web increase pen drive from the
bridge as fast as possible will increase its speed
and now reach from thinking will
try and do it as quickly as possible or
else they are still another political crisis of
processes and day proceed or else you
again mean whoever you are or you will wait for
tomorrow that he should leave first
after that you will go this point on the
headlines and pass dress you will burn your headlines
and then you will go or now keep blowing the
horn so indicate grandma-aunt
in work so you tell yourself visit
now tell yourself that you  What will you do in this situation? This happens
many times, it is a true
mission when we are somewhere remote or in a state of
ego, then
such a situation arises,
what will you do at that time, please do tell us in this situation
and we would request that you
join this entire camp
with your family and friends and you have a
chance to get one multiple multiply
price sub part of the road safety shoes
Amazon in 9 days, people do not think that it is
so big because firstly,
people die due to diseases and
road accidents, do you know that
not as many people die due to diseases as many
people lose their lives in this road, that is, road accidents,
more of us, so the people who are
here are the generation which we will let come, that is the
generation which loses its family
due to a small negligence, so
if we can
modify ourselves a little bit in that way, we can bring about
those changes in ourselves  If we can
follow the road traffic rules, then
somewhere or the other we will be
able to make our day safer. So, I request you to
kindly join this campaign along with your
family and friends and together with Indian
Rozgar CO Lalganj and using the road every
day. It is not that only one person
uses the road, on a daily basis, from small to
big, everyone uses the road, be it to
drive to school, to go to the
market or to
go to relatives, or if you have to go anywhere, then
you have to use it every day. So,
we will have to teach this to ourselves as well as our
children so that
they can stay safe on the road. Now
I will look at the screen.
You have only 2 hours.
After 2 hours, we will add another one with
not one question and will share the
question with you. So, you have 2 hours
for this question. Such a Dashrath question and so
Dev see, you can be a part of this.  Along
with your family and friends, this is
actually you Bhains Ring Road Safety View
Pramod Ring Road Safety I want you to
leg Abhinav yaar on the road benefit which inside
everyday please do not do anything that
your family and you will have to regret
a small carelessness can take someone's life
please stay safe and follow all these
safety rules
you can see on the screen question your
approaching Nehru Bridge Yadav when
entrepreneurs from subscribe now
you are about to enter one bridge and you
see that the other one is about to enter the bridge
from the other side what will you do at that time
increase subscribe you will
try to
cross the bridge as fast as possible many vehicular
processes will forcefully dandruff dandruff media will wait
that the other one will
cross the bridge and then the affair will go Ashraf
this point on the headlight inspector bridge will
now turn on the light and press the fabric
this continues till continuously to
indicate you emergency or now condition by blowing the horn  You will be surprised
that you are coming and he stops, then
tell us as quickly as possible what will you do in that situation, so what has happened is that the
enemy of all this despite safety and cities of
concern is inclined this poll campaign is ring road
safety and without youtube se noose daily
100 grams of tamarind India news all the
safety measures and bases and made the road of increasing with
answers in this will come together
for this noble cause no one
feels that interest
is so important or anything but help us people if you
go and see in that way then it is a
very major concern those people who do
not take this thing seriously, if you are
driving then wearing a helmet is very
important and not only for you, if
someone is sitting behind you also
wearing a helmet is equally important, people do not even understand this thing that the
helmet
shampoo is for our seat, if you fall then the person in
front does not keep all this and
if the person sitting behind also says it then they should
also be equally careful  They can get hurt and they can even lose their lives
there, any celery can be
attached to it, so whenever you sit
on the bikes, both of you should wear helmets, wear this
mask,
Jai Hind
and tell me, you
can see all this on the screen
that you have the chance to win more exciting
prizes in Hindi of top 10
school campaign and you can contribute by
joining it and applying these things
in your daily life, you have not come right on the stomach,
this losing is happening otherwise don't get angry, thank you so
much specific turmeric please follow these
rules in that awards specific you so much u that
tumor different department Vijendra set up
question